I've walked through all these halls before
这里走廊我全走过
I've been in and out of every door,
教室进出新知也无多
There's nothin' in this school that I don't know
学校的信息尽在我掌握
In every class, my grade's the best
课程成绩这一切
The highest score on every test
对我都简单无差别
I think that means it's time for me to go
我想这代表是时候远走
I know there's more that's out there
未知存在~这世界
And I just haven't found it yet
只是我不曾去了解
I know there's more that's out there
未知存在~这世界
Another me I haven't met
新的自我等待迎接
This school is full of people
学校满是学生
But still I don't belong
而我未融入其中
They only dream of winning
他们只想自己赢
Look at me like something's wrong
所以视我为蠹虫
Maybe I'm better off alone
也许最好孤独至终
Will I find what I'm lookin' for
可要是我独自生活
If I just do it on my own?
能否找到毕生所衷？
I know there's more that's out there
未知存在~这世界
Something to fill this hole inside
可以填补内心空白
I know there's more that's out there
未知存在~这世界
And I'm not afraid to try
我已经迫不及待
There's only so much this school can offer
学校教我的只有这么多
And I'm not saying that it's wrong
我并非说学校有错
But I know there's more that's out there
但未知遍布这世界
'Cause I've been searching all along
我将一直寻找至终
Beyond these rooms, beyond these walls
房间之后，墙壁外廓~~
So much to learn, I can't see it all
还有很多未曾见识过
There's somethin' out there callin' me
外界呼唤我去寻觅~~
And it's a mystery that I can't wait to see
它晦涩又神秘 我已经等不及
Cause I know there's more that's out there
因为未知遍布这世界
Another place, another way
就在前面 某个方位
And I know there's more that's out there
就算未知遍布这世界
And I'll find out someday!
答案终在结尾！
I'll find out someday...
就在那结尾…